sheeel.com 2013-09-20

# Sheeel ... A Deal Everyday Privacy Policy

##### Scope

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on the sheeel.com websites. It applies generally to the sheeel.com website and content and other related websites where this policy appears in the footer of the page. Some sheeel.com-branded websites or websites we operate may be governed by separate privacy policies. The policy that applies on any of our domains or subdomains is always the policy that appears in the footer of each website.

Our subsidiaries’ and joint ventures’ privacy practices are similar to those described in this Privacy Policy. Subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the sheeel.com website. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on January 16, 2011.

##### Collection

You can browse our sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers.

We may collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address, physical contact information;
  * transactional information based on your activities on the sites;
  * shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item;
  * dispute resolution, correspondence through our sites, and correspondence sent to us;
  * other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information;
  * additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity or ownership of an item you list);
  * information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties (for example, if you incur a debt to sheeel.com, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law).

We do not intentionally collect information from persons under thirteen years of age.

##### Marketing

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our ad-customization programs, simply indicate your preference in your profile on sheeel.com or by following the directions provided with the communication or advertisement.

##### Use

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * tell you about our services and those of our corporate family, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

##### Our Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your personal information with:

  * Members of the sheeel.com company family to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you’ve requested their services.
  * Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards).
  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).
  * Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history.
  * Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.)

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

##### Information You Share on sheeel.com

Your User ID is displayed throughout sheeel.com and is connected to all of your sheeel.com activity. If you access our sites from a shared computer or a computer in an internet café, certain information about you, such as your User ID, activity or reminders from sheeel.com, may also be visible to other individuals who use the computer after you.

##### Cookies

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety.

A few important things you should know about cookies are that:

  * We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies.
  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services.
  * You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the sites that we do not control. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page.)

##### No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing

We and our users do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your sheeel.com communication preferences so we communicate to you as you prefer. You are not licensed to add other sheeel.com users, even a user who has purchased an item from you, to your mailing list (email or physical mail) without their express consent. To report sheeel.com-related spam or spoof emails to sheeel.com, please forward the email to [cs@sheeel.com](mailto:cs@sheeel.com). We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content.

##### Account Protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your sheeel.com password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify sheeel.com and change your password.

##### Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to sheeel.com. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our sheeel.com User Agreement and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

##### Security

Your information is stored on our servers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

##### Financial Information

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction is completed, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

##### Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Sheeel.com does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

##### General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the site. In addition, we will notify you through the sheeel.com Message Center. If your questions are not answered online, you may email us on [cs@sheeel.com](mailto:cs@sheeel.com) or write to us at:

Sheeel.com, Tawseel General Trading

_Street Address:_

Sharq, Block 6, Building 51

Kuwait City, Kuwait

_Post Office Address:_

PO Box 3722 Sabah Al Salem,

Zip Code: 44531

Kuwait
